Christopher Warren

+1-415-200-3456 | github.com/cwarrendotco/

christopher@cwarren.co

San Francisco, CA

Recent grad and United States Air Force (USAF) Veteran with experience in project and program management, process design and optimization, and strategic planning. Takes pride in being an excellent communicator who can distill complex technical concepts into easy to digest packages for any audience. Loves getting passionate about work and diving into the weeds.

Education

B.S. Management Information Systems

SFSU | Anticipated Grad Spring 2018

Coursework: JavaScript, SQL, CSS, HTML, Python, JQuery, Excel

A.S. Electronic Systems Technology

Community College of the Air Force | 2015

Other Coursework

Splunk E-Learning, Salesforce Trailhead Sales Engineering Trailmix

Work Experience

Network Analyst Intern

September 2017 - December 2016

San Francisco State University

Assisted with setup and installation of new switching equipment to facilitate IT control and oversight of campus housing network infrastructure.

Project Manager for Exercises, Plans, and Programs

January 2015 - January 2016

USAF, 726th Air Control Squadron

Hand-selected for 3 person cross-functional team that successfully prepared 300 employees and \$104 million in equipment for Exercise Red Flag on a one year timeline.

- Planned and executed 9 network training exercises. Designed communication networks spanning multiple information systems (voice, satellite, radio, and IP) and presented executives with flexible range of budgetary solutions.
- Developed and managed monthly driver training program; scouted 600 mile route, with 8 heavy trucks per convoy. Arranged fuel and meal funding and approval from outside agencies.
 Qualified 192 employees and delivered a 100% success rate.
- Experienced at tailoring presentations to audiences across the organization; from technical training sessions to concise executive briefings.
- Managed 5.5k item company-wide equipment inventory. Completed 2 weeks ahead of schedule, secured \$230k funding to resolve 2 year inventory shortfall.
- Acted as liaison between executives and field technicians. Developed executive needs into technical realities while also efficiently communicating technical possibilities upwards.

Radio Frequency Transmissions Systems Supervisor

November 2012 - January 2015

USAF, 726th Air Control Squadron

Managed maintenance and inspection of \$10M of satellite, radio, and microwave equipment while implementing training and qualifications program for a four person maintenance and inspection team.

- Collaborated with service provider to engineer novel equipment configuration, reducing equipment overhead and simplifying architecture during critical infrastructure upgrade.
- Revised 300 pages of technical documentation and implemented procedures to optimize maintenance processes; shaved 3 hours off 4 hour maintenance procedure.
- Ran technical product showcase for top-level officials, demonstrating equipment capabilities.